BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/014
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14)
1952-1976
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS)
6178/014
11.5 cubic feet
11.5 linear ft.
Records (documents), collective labor agreements.
5833680
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, July 07, 2005
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 19, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The US Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) was established in 1884 to collect information about employment and labor in the United States. As mandated by the 1947 Taft-Hartley Act, the BLS was formally tasked with responsibility for soliciting, collecting, and analyzing collective bargaining agreements (CBAs) from public and private establishments, and making the agreements publicly available. In the early 1980s, this was function was limited to union contracts made with employers of 1000 or more employees.
In 2002, the National Archives and Records Administration authorized the BLS to donate inactive, non-confidential agreements which were 5 years or more past their expiration date to the Kheel Center where they would be preserved and made available to the public. The Office of Labor-Management Services took over responsibility for collecting and analyzing CBAs in 2011, and continues this donor relationship with the Kheel Center.
Scope and Contents
The US Department of Labor Historical Collective Bargaining Agreements Collection, 6178, is made up of 21 series of expired public- and private-sector collective bargaining agreements dating from 1887 to 2003 and totals 685 linear feet plus 10 CDs of digitized documents and 320 reels of microfilm. In addition to the CBAs, a small volume of related documents such as union constitutions, pension and health plans submitted to the BLS, are also available.
Selected collective bargaining agreements from this collection were digitized with generous funding from the National Historic Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC), and the National Science Foundation (NSF). Because documents other than collective bargaining agreements were also collected and preserved here by the US Department of Labor, a folder containing material that has been digitized, may also contain material which has not been digitized such as constitutions, bylaws, working rules, life insurance plans, or other organizational documents. For access to non-digitized material, contact Kheel Center staff.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/023: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
Industrial relations -- United States; Collective labor agreements - United States.; Labor unions -- United States.; United States. Department of Labor -- Archives; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics -- Archives; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics. Division of Industrial Relations -- Archives; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics. Office of Wages and Industrial Relations -- Archives; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers-- Archives; United Steelworkers of America-- Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America -- Archives; United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America-- Archives; United Sugar workers' Council of California-- Archives; Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union-- Archives; Lithographers and Photoengravers International Union -- Archives; Service Employees International Union-- Archives; Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers-- Archives; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers -- Archives
5833680
- Code no.24: Avco Corporation and IBEW Local 1127, 1963-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Code no.1101: Jefferson City Cabinet Company and IUE Local 748, 1958-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Code no.3237: Hughes Tool Company and Independent Metal Workers Union Locals 1 and 2, 1957-1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Code no.3251: Kearney and Trecker Corporation and Employees' Independent Union, 1959-1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Code no.3256: Warner and Swasey Company and IAM Local 1253, 1960-1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Code no.3266: Whitin Machine Works and United Steelworkers of America, 1959-1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Code no.3278: Timken Roller Bearing Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Code no.3301: Whirlpool Corporation and Refrigeration Workers, Warehousemen, Drivers, and Helpers Local 827, 1960-1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Code no.3302: Koppers Company, Inc. and IAM Lodge 1784, 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Code no.3313: Avco Corporation, New Idea Division and United Steelworkers of America, 1963-1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Code no.3319: J.I. Case Company and UAW Local 180, 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Code no.3320: Page Aircraft Maintenance, Inc. and IAM Local 2003, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Code no.3322: Danly Machine Specialties, Inc. and United Mine Workers of America Local 15271, 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Code no.3602: I-T-E Circuit Breaker Company and Electrical Switchgear Union, 1958-1966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Code no.3606: Square D Company and IBEW Local 1169, 1960-1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Code no.3637: Maytag Company and UAW Local 997, 1961-1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Code no.3641: Sunbeam Corporation and IAM District 8, 1958-1967 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Code no.3645: Illumination Products, Inc. and IBEW Local 3, 1961-1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Code no.3649: Admiral Corporation and IBEW Local 1031, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Code no.3658: Magnavox Company of Tennessee and IUE Local 796, 1961-1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Code no.3709: Magnavox Company of Tennessee and Allied Industrial Workers of America Local 254, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Code no.3712: Avco Corporation, Electronics Division and IBEW Local 1842, 1962-1966 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Code no.4047: Avco Corporation, Lycoming Division and UAW Local 787, 1959-1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Code no.4048: Avco Corporation, Lycoming Division and UAW Local 1010, 1961-1967 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Code no.4135: Avco Corporation, Nashville Division and IAM Lodge 735, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Code no.2931: Independent Metal Trade Companies in California and IAM Lodge 15, 1961-1968 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Code no.2932: Iron League of Philadelphia and Vicinity and Shopmen's Local Union 502, 1959-1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Code no.2935: Structural Steel and Ornamental Iron Association of New Jersey, Inc. and Shopmen's Local Union 545, 1959-1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Code no.2945: American Chain and Cable Company, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Code no.3203: Briggs and Stratton Corporation and Allied Industrial Workers of America Local 232, 1962-1967 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Code no.3204: Elliott Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1963-1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Code no.3206: Continental Motors Corporation and UAW Local 113, 1958-1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Code no.3210: Fairbanks, Morse, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America Local 1533, 1961-1967 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Code no.3212: Johnson Motors and Independent Marine and Machinists Association, 1960-1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Code no.3214: Worthington Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1959-1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Code no.3222: John Deere Planter Works and UAW Locals 94, 79, 838, 74, 865, 450, 434, 1958-1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Code no.3227: Minneapolis-Moline Company and UAW Local 1146, 1959-1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Code no.3228: Oliver Corporation and UAW Local 1315, 1961-1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Code no.3230: Bucyrus-Erie Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1967 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Code no.3232: Caterpillar Tractor Co. and UAW Local 751, 1961-1967 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Code no.21: General Dynamics/Pomona and IAM District 120, Lodges 1233, 1254, 1960-1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Code no.3654: General Dynamics/Electronics and Rochester Independent Workers Local 1, 1961-1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Code no.3659: Radio Corporation of America and IUE Local 177, 103, 771, 110, 106, 439, 1961-1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Code no.3717: General Dynamics/Stromberg-Carlson Division and IUE Local 338, 1962-1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Code no.4073: General Dynamics/Fort Worth Division and IAM Lodge 776, 1960-1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Code no.4074: General Dynamics/Fort Worth Division and Office Employees International Union Local 277, 1960-1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Code no.4103: General Dynamics/Electric Boat Division and Metal Trades Council, 1960-1968 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Code no.4104: General Dynamics/Electric Boat Division and Marine Draftsmen's Association, 1961-1966 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Code no.3660: Radio Corporation of America and IBEW Local 1160, 1961-1967 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Code no.3661: Radio Corporation of America and American Federation of Technical Engineers Local 241, 1959-1968 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Code no.3662: Radio Corporation of America and Association of Scientists and Professional Engineering Personnel, 1961-1964 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Code no.3297: Hussmann Refrigerator Co. and American Federation of Labor and Affiliated Organizations, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Code no.3659: Radio Corporation of America and IUE Local 103, 1959-1962 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Code no.3694: Radio Corporation of America and Radio Communications Assemblers Union, Inc., 1961-1967 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Code no.7936: RCA Service Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1962-1968 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Code no.3609: Allen-Bradley Company and IUE Local 1111, 1961-1967 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Code no.3614: Cutler-Hammer, Inc. and IAM Local 1061, 1960-1968 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Code no.3615: Emerson Electric Manufacturing Co. and IUE Local 1102, 1959-1967 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Code no.3616: Fansteel Metallurgical Corporation and IAM Lodge 1777, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Code no.1900: Armstrong Rubber Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America Locals 93, 164, 283, 303, 1961- 1967 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Code no.1901: Dayton Tire and Rubber Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America Local 178, 1960- 1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Code no.1905: General Tire and Rubber Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America Locals 9, 312, 1961- 1967 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Code no.1908: Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Code no.1912: U.S. Rubber Tire Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America Local 101, 1964-1967 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Code no.2323: General Refractories Company and United Brick and Clay Workers of America Local 763, 1960-1967 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Code no.2324: General Refractories Company and United Mine Workers of America Local 14643, 1962-1967 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Code no.2332: Carborundum Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Local 8-12058, 1969-1969 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Code no.2344: Southwestern Portland Cement Co. and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers Union Local 49, 1963-1967 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Code no.2352: Lehigh Portland Cement Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers Union Local 129, 1967-1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Code no.2501: Interlake Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1967 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Code no.2510: Bethlehem Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Code no.2514: Continental Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America Local 1054, 1959-1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Code no.2516: Copperweld Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Code no.2517: Crucible Steel Company of America and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Code no.2520: Empire-Reeves Steel Corp. and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Code no.2535: Northwestern Steel and Wire Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Code no.2535: Parrish-Alford Fence and Machine Company, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Code no.2557: Blaw-Knox Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1967 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Code no.2586: Phelps Dodge Corporation and International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers Locals 616, 551, 470, 1959- 1967 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Code no.2610: Reynolds Metals Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1959-1968 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Code no.2909: True Temper Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1962-1966 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Code no.2912: American Radiator and Standard Sanitary Corporation and Standard Allied Trades Council, 1960-1969 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Code no.2918: Scovil Manufacturing Company and UAW Local 1604, 1957-1966 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Code no.2926: California Metal Trades Association and IAM, 1961-1968 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Code no.2927: Combustion Engineering, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Lodge 656, 1960-1969 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Code no.2957: Kohler Co. and UAW Local 833, 1962-1968 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Code no.305: Stephen F. Whitman and Son, Inc. and American Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union Local 439, 1959- 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Code no.316: National Distillers Products Company and Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers International Union of America Local 11, 1961-1968 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Code no.317: New Jersey Brewers Association and Brewery Workers Joint Local Executive Board of New Jersey, 1959-1964 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Code no.319: Schenley Distillers, Inc. and Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers International Union of America Local 53, 1961- 1966 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Code no.349: Dairy Employer's Labor Council and Milk Drivers, Dairy and Creamery Workers Local 66, 1963-1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Code no.1216: Kimberly-Clark Corporation and United Mine Workers of America Local 12970, 1961-1971 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Code no.1633: E.I. DuPont De Nemours and Company and Seaford Nylon Employees' Council, Inc., 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Code no.1641: Union Carbide Plastic Company and Chemicals and Crafts Union, Inc., 1960-1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Code no.1644: Merck and Co. and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Locals 12-86, 12-580, 13-575, 1960-1964 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Code no.1650: Lever Brothers Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Local 7-366, 1961-1970 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Code no.18: Olin Mathieson Chemical Corporation and District 9, International Association of Machinists, 1958-1968 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Code no.217: John Morrell and Co. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Locals 304, 665, 530, 1959-1970 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Code no.224: Alameda County Milk Dealers and Milk Drivers, Dairy Employees Union Local 302, 1961-1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Code no.225: Associated Milk Dealers, Inc. and Dairy Employees' Union Local 754, 1959-1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Code no.230: Greater Pittsburgh Milk Dealers Association and Milk and Ice Cream Salesmen, Drivers and Dairy Employees Local 205, 1960- 1967 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Code no.283: Milk Wagon Employers and Milk Wagon Drivers Local 603, 1959-1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Code no.240: Greater New York Milk Dealers Labor Committee and Milk Drivers Locals 584, 602, 607, 1961-1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Code no.246: Evergreen Frozen Foods Company and IBT Local 780, 1961-1968 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Code no.248: Blue Lake Packers, Inc. and Cannery Warehousemen, Food Processors, Drivers and Helpers Local 670, 1960-1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Code no.254: Campbell Soup Company and Food Process Workers and Warehousemen Local 228, 1960-1968 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Code no.255: Campbell Soup Company and United Packinghouse Food and Allied Workers of America, 1960-1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Code no.260: Packing House Employers and Warehousemen's Union Local 616, 1960-1967 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Code no.262: Pineapple Companies and ILWU Local 142, 1960-1968 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Code no.268: General Mills, Inc. and American Federation of Grain Millers, 1960-1969 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Code no.271: Pillsbury Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, 1960-1969 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Code no.277: Federation of New England Bakery Employers and New England Bakery Drivers Council Local 686, 1962-1969 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Code no.282: National Biscuit Company and National Biscuit Division of the Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union, 1957- 1967 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Code no.288: Sunshine Biscuits, Inc. and Biscuit and Cracker Union Local 525, 1953-1968 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Code no.290: Wholesale Bakers Group and Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union Locals 37, 31, 1960-1967 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Code no.293: Amalgamated Sugar Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, Sugar Division, 1959-1968 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Code no.297: American Crystal Sugar Company and United Sugar Workers' Council of California, 1959-1968 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Code no.297: Holly Sugar Corporation and United Sugar Workers' Council of California, 1959-1968 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Code no.297: Spreckels Sugar Company and United Sugar Workers' Council of California, 1959-1968 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Code no.300: Sugar Plantation Companies Negotiating Committee and ILWU Local 142, 1961-1969 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Code no.1: ACF Industries, Albuquerque Division and IAM Lodge 794, 1963-1968 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Code no.611: Erwin Mills, Inc. and Textile Workers Union of America, 1961-1969 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Code no.2515: Superior Steel Division of Copperweld Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 171, 1960-1962 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Code no.2589: Perth Amboy Plant of American Smelting and Refining Company and Perth Amboy Smelter and Refinery Workers' Union, 1959- 1967 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Code no.2916: Manufacturers Industrial Relations Association and International Molders' and Allied Workers' Union of North America, 1962- 1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Code no.4075: General Dynamics Convair and IAM District 50, Lodge 1125, 1960-1965 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Code no.4095: United Aircraft Corporation and IAM Lodge 743, 1960-1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Code no.4118: Baldwin-Lima-Hamilton Corporation and United Steelworkers of America Locals 1278, 2180, 2443, 1960-1965 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Code no.4121: Pullman-Standard and Brotherhood Railway Carmen of America Local 290, 1959-1969 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Code no.4124: Budd Company and UAW Locals 92, 306, 813, 1122, 1961-1968 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Code no.4125: Trailmobile, Division of Pullman, Inc. and UAW Local 392, 1961-1968 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Code no.4133: Mack Trucks, Inc. and UAW Local 171, 1962-1964 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Code no.4406: General Controls Co. and IAM Lodge 1600, 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Code no.4413: Sperry Gyroscope Company and Engineers Association, 1958-1962 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Code no.4419: Elgin National Watch Co. and Elgin National Watch Workers' Union, 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Code no.4430: Barber-Colman Company and Sheet Metal Workers International Association Local 573, 1964-1967 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Code no.4601: Baldwin Piano Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 5397, 1959-1961 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Code no.4602: Wurlitzer Company and IUE, 1960-1963 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Code no.4603: Brunswick-Balke-Collender Co. and IAM Local 1813, 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Code no.4605: Lionel Corporation and IUE Local 430, 1961-1965 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Code no.5202: Carriers Council of New Hampshire, Inc. and IBT Local 633, 1957-1967 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Code no.5207: Driveaway Employers Negotiating Committee and IBT Eastern Conference, 1958-1967 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Code no.5409: National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association and Pacific Maritime Association, 1958-1965 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Code no.5706: California Water and Telephone Company and IBEW Local 1008, 1960-1968 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Code no.5708: Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company of West Virginia and CWA, 1960-1969 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Code no.5718: General Telephone Company of Wisconsin and CWA, 1961-1972 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Code no.8661: National Transient Members and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, 1960-1968 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Code no.540860: New England Road Builders' Association, Inc. and Hoisting and Portable Engineers Local Union 478, 1964-1973 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Code no.541547: Honeywell Inc., Industrial Division and Metal Trades Local 705, 1967-1972 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Code no.550130: Federal-Mogul Corporation, National Seal Division and UAW Local 109, 1964-1969 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Code no.550180: Beech-Nut, Inc. and Beech-Nut Cooperative Council, 1964-1972 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Code no.550260: B.F. Nelson Folding Cartons, Inc. and Warehousemen, Drivers and Helpers Union Local 359, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Code no.550731: California Conference Mason Contractors' Association and Hodcarriers' Local 291, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Code no.550377: St. Regis Paper Company and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Local 307, 1964- 1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Code no.550682: Conestoga Transportation Company and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees, 1964-1973 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Code no.550880: United States Plywood Corp. and Industrial Workers of America Local 3-140, 1963-1969 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Code no.550972: Oliver Corporation and IAM Local 1633, 1964-1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Code no.551056: Out-State Builders Association and Laborer's International Union of North America Local 1148, 1966-1970 (Box 9, Folder 11)